是的。
Yeah.
那么为什么不呢
So why don't
你去吧。
you go ahead.
并分享一首诗
And share a poem
我一直在努力？
I've been
working on?
我不想。
I don't want to.
但 Proven 说我必须这样做。
But Proven said
I had to.
所以我没有说你必须这样做。
So I didn't say
you had to.
它被称为这个地方是狗屎。
It's called
This Place is shit.
哦，很好。
Oh, good.
这个地方是狗屎。
This place is shit.
这个地方闻起来像狗屎。
This place
smells like shit.
贝茜的声音听起来像狗屎。
Bessie's voice
sounds like shit.
癌症狗屎。
Cancer shit.
奥斯卡
Oscar
那傻吗
does that stupid
他想走就走
walk when he wants
为了隐藏他的狗屎，他的裤子。
to hide his shit,
his pants.
弥尔顿有狗屎
And Milton has shit
音乐品味。
taste in music.
这还没完。
It's not finished.
那太好了。
That was great.
让我们。
Let's.
我要为此鼓掌。
I'm going to clap
for that.
不要鼓掌。
Don't clap for.
我要为它鼓掌。
I'm going to clap
for it.
鼓掌。
Clap for.
你的玩得怎么样？
How's your play?
伟大。
Great.
感谢今天的分享。
Thanks for sharing
today.
很多亵渎，但我。
A lot of profanity,
but I.
我不欣赏这个评论
I didn't appreciate
the comment
关于奥斯卡的便便散步。
about Oscar's poop
walk.
奥斯卡觉得这很有趣。
Oscar thought
it was funny.
这很有趣，但它仍然很刻薄。
It was funny, but
it was still mean.
我是一个非常刻薄的人。
I'm a very mean
person.
这是一个非常开放的认识。
That's a very open
realization.
我早就知道了。
I've known that
for a while.
嘿，我们要展示半小时。
Hey, we're going to
show half an hour.
哦，看，到那时我可能已经死了。
Oh, see, I might be
dead by then.
哦，是的，你可能会。
Oh, yeah, you might.
但如果你没有死，它就很短。
But if you're not
dead, it's short.
而且它在城市里。
And it's in
the city.
你上一次是什么时候
When's the last
time you
在城里吗？
were in the city?
上次
Last time
应该是最后一次。
was supposed
to be the last time.
另一个时间在哪里？
Where's
another time?
如果我们吃披萨，我就去。
I'll go
if we get pizza.
我们昨天可以吃披萨吗？
Can we have pizza
yesterday?
你吃了吗？不。
Did you eat it? No.
那不是披萨。
That wasn't pizza.
好。
Okay.
嗯，那么，是的，
Well, then, yeah,
我们会在回来的路上吃披萨。
we'll get pizza
on the way back.
在城市里。
In the city.
我去换衣服。
I'll go get changed.
好吧。
All right.
如果您需要帮助，请告诉凯蒂。
Let Katie know
if you need help.
是的。
Yeah.
安静。
Quiet.
变得更好。
Getting better.
好吧，伙计们。
All right, guys.
这有点陡峭
This is a little bit
steep
抓住栏杆。
to grab on
to the railing.
你知道，从来都不是好事，也不是坏事。
You know,
and never good, bad.
就像，首先
Like, first
父亲下去了，就像，上升了。
father goes down
and, like, goes up.
这是一场木偶戏。
It's a puppet show.
这是一场牵线木偶表演。
It's a marionette
show.
我们是牵线木偶。
We are marionette.
你撒谎。
You lie.
我不知道我是不是撒谎了。
I don't know
if I lie.
您可以查看时间表。
You can check
the schedule.
你绊倒了吗？
You tripped?
哦，是的。
Oh, yeah.
我试着施加压力。
I tried to pressure.
一段引人入胜的历史。
A fascinating
history.
这些话，实际上是一个参考。
The words, actually,
a reference.
致圣母玛利亚
To the Virgin Mary
就像。
was like.
这是佛罗多。
This is Frodo.
我画画
I draw
没有游戏。
no game.
就这个，就这个。
Just this,
just this.
我欠你多少钱？
How much do
I owe you?
嘿，多少钱？
Hey, how much?
这是 4 美元。
It's $4.
而且你不能在这里养猫。
And you can't have
a cat in here.
这是一只服务猫。
It's a service cat.
不，我认识你。
No, I know you.
我听到了你们所有人的声音。
I hear you all.
全部聚集起来
Gather all up
并尽快上车。
and get on the bus
as soon as I can.
你好？
Hello?
你好。
Hello.
哦，是的
Oh, yeah,
是的。
yeah.
就像您支付一样
Just as you paying
三。
three.
所以，听着，
So, listen,
我们现在必须回去。再见。
we have to head back
now. Bye.
有些事情正在发生
Something's
happening
在城市里，
in the city,
他们希望我们回来，杰森。
and they want us
back, Jason.
但我们先吃披萨。
But we're getting
pizza first.
不，我们得安排。
No, we're going
to have to arrange.
一切都是为了让他们可以等待。
Everything
so they can wait.
这只是披萨。
It's just pizza.
山 姆。改天我们再吃披萨。
Sam. We'll get pizza
another day.
我们已经在城里了。
We're already
in the city.
好吧，那么今晚订购。
Well, then order it
tonight.
只需在城市里得到它。
Just get it
in the city.
什么？
What?
我们在城里吃披萨
We're getting pizza
in the city
然后我们回去。
and then we'll go
back.
不，我们不会去。
No, we're not going.
是的。我们得到了。
Yes. We are getting.
你得冷静下来。冷静。
You got to calm
down. Calm down.
别告诉我。冷静。
Don't tell me.
Calm down.
我不和你争论。
I don't argue
with you.
我只是。我是你的朋友，好吗？
I'm just. I'm
your friend, okay?
你不是我的朋友。
You're not
my friend.
你是一名护士。
You're a nurse.
你上了车。
You get on the bus.
是的，上车。我是
Yeah,
get on the bus. I'm
Microsoft 用于
Microsoft for
a. Flash 和。
a. Flash and.
现在大家
Now everyone
会纠正我的。
would right my.
妈的。时间
Shit. Time
警笛
sirens
一分。
one point.
19115497.
哦，五。
Oh five.
撤离该区域，而不是
Evacuate
the area, not
疏散。
evacuate.
100小时。
100 hours.
当您遇到这种情况时，就会发生这种情况
That happens
when you
旅行
travel
周围。长
around. Long
从一个
from one
一半。
one half.
到一个
To one
路。
road.
疏散工作已经开始。现在。
Evacuations
are beginning. Now.
南街海港
South Street Seaport
向南行驶要格外小心。
travel south with
extreme caution.
这是一个。
This is a.
强制疏散令。
Mandatory
evacuation order.
我们仍然处于以下状态。
We remain under.
攻击。
Attack.
在水上寻求庇护。
Seek shelter
on water.
你的口袋不会游泳。
Your pockets cannot
swim.
两次疏散。
Both evacuations.
现在开始
Are beginning now
在南街海港
in the South Street
Seaport
从地方。
from place.
自。地方。
To. Place.
哦，伙计。
Oh, man.
乔纳森
Jonathan,
巴士
the bus
拿走了。
took.
它很多
Its much
人
people
向南走，
to go south,
看看他们的船。
see their boats.
你需要停止一些
You need to
stop some
运动。是的。
movement. Yes.
好。
Okay.
逃
Escape
那不是
that doesn't
想来。
want to come.
让我们只是。
Let's just.
让我们摆脱伤害。
Let's get out
of harm's way.
留在某个地方。
Keep someplace.
是的。
Yeah.
您可以向此项目作出贡献
You could help
它。用一只脚出去。
it. Out with a foot.
浪。
Wave.
哦，等等
Ooh, wait
一分钟。
a minute.
哦，你看。
Oh, you look.
你感觉很糟糕。
You feel bad.
娜塔莉。
Natalie.
在这里，我触摸你可以去的地方。
Here, I touch
where you can go.
哦，没关系。
Oh, it's all right.
还有那个锚，我来了，
And the anchor,
I came here,
学校。
the school.
只是我做的一件事
Just the one thing I
本来应该做的。
was supposed to do.
你得去水边。
You got to get to
the water.
我离开了城市。
I get out
of the city.
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
我要去吃披萨。
I'm going to get
pizza.
井。
Well.
贝茜在哈莱姆区。
Basie's up
in Harlem.
我认为世界。可能要结束了。
I think the world.
Might be ending.
我认为这是一个糟糕的赛季设置。
I think this is bad
season setting up.
这是最后 11 句话
That is the last
11 says
我会得到的。
I'm going to get.
好
Okay,
okay,
好。
okay.
我们来吃披萨吧。
Let's get pizza.
不，我要吃披萨。
No, I'm
getting pizza.
你运行了这个吗？
Did you run this?
是的，但现在不是了。
Yeah,
but not anymore.
事实并非如此。
It's not.
那是我爸爸。
That's my dad.
我的钢琴。
My piano.
你玩
You play
尽可能。
as possible.
拜托，我可以来拿吗
Please,
can I come and get
和你一起吃披萨？
pizza with you?
右。这
Right. This
他说想要。
he said wanted.
要使用
To use
它。已经两年了。
it. It's been two.
你说 4 到 6 个月。
You said
4 to 6 months.
已经六年了。
It has been six.
这对我来说是免费的。
And this is free
to me.
减去我。
Subtraction me.
加法。
Addition.
我被告知这个简单的数学。
And I was told
this simple math.
在我的生活中
In my life
我从来没有。
and I never.
需要更多，更多
Needed more, a more
或更少
or less
下降到三个
to fall to three
到小。
to small.
而且小。井
And small. Well
直到一个月。
until month.
今天的
Today's
它是
it was
生病了，
to sick,
但不是现在。
but not now.
我的小学校
My little school
我有
I had
在那个时候对他来说是什么。
what to him
at that point.
我想如果我没有。
And I think
if I didn't.
获取材料。
Get the materials.
像这些合同
Like these contract
得到诊断。
get diagnosed.
我只是
I just
我爱
I loved
当我看到他打球时
when it took me
to see him playing
在爵士乐俱乐部
at a jazz club
by 贝茜
by Betsy
并做
and doing
嗯，恰好有
well happen to have
死。
died.
哦，这很难
Oh it's hard
要有婴儿钢琴
to have baby piano
我们是。
we were.
停下船。
Stop the boat.
停下船
Stop the boat
你了解你。
you know you.